Newton Yan

Passionate front-end web developer with 3 years of experience in creating visually engaging and responsive web applications. Strong problem-solving skills and able to work collaboratively in a team environment. Eager to learn new technologies and adapting to new challenges.

yankaiyin@hotmail.com (647) 616-6144 www.newtonyan.com Toronto, ON, Canada

Experience

Belun Technology Company Limited

Programmer Analyst | Sep 2021 – Apr 2023

- Analyzed user requirements and designed solutions that meet their needs
- Collaborated with the backend team and developed new web applications with lonic(Angular) and SvelteKit
- Provided technical support and troubleshooting for existing web applications
- Implemented company website improvements and enhancements
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams by leveraging issue and project tracking tools like JIRA

Automated Systems (H.K.) Limited

Analyst Programmer | Dec 2020 – Sep 2021

- Developed responsive web application with Vue.js
- Developed a REST API using Spring framework
- Collaborated with end-users to define application requirements

Programmer | Dec 2019 – Dec 2020

- Developed web application with Java and Apache Struts Framework
- Implemented improvements and enhancements on existing web application (.NET framework)

Information Technology Services Centre, CUHK

Student Helper | Jul 2018 – Jul 2019

• Designed multimedia courseware using Adobe Premiere Pro, After Effects

Education

The Chinese University of Hong Kong

B.Eng in Systems Engineering and Engineering Management

- Second Class Upper Division
- Major GPA: 3.480/4.000

Awards and Honors

- Outstanding Students Awards 2019
- The Professor Julie Hung Hsua Yu Scholarship for Intellectual Excelleration
- The Yen Scholarship for Academic Excellence

Skills

Usability testing
Project management
User research